RG 009, Office of the Attorney General
Connecticut State Library
Office of the Attorney General records
1666-2008
bulk 1890-2008
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Office of the Attorney General
cubic feet
RG009
Multiple
Historical Note
Before 1897, Connecticut did not have an Attorney General. In April 1897, the House introduced H.B. 344 to create the office of Attorney General to supervise all legal matters in which the State is an interested party. The Governor would appoint the official with the approval by the Senate. After the Judiciary committee twice rejected the bill, the House amended it to make the office elective. Charles Phelps, a Republican from Vernon served as the first Attorney General from 1899-1903.
See also the and.
Scope and Content
The records were arranged into 4 subgroups and 8 series which document the. The series include.
Series 1. Correspondence, 1899-1947,
Series 2. Case Files,, consists of correspondence; notes; invoices; newspaper clippings; exhibits; reports; motions; petitions; appearance notices; trial lists; extensions; briefs; demurrers; petition, bill of review, and application; complaints, application, order to show cause and writ; order and writ; application to be made a party; short calendar post cards; memorandum of decision; rulings; findings; motions to remand; bills of cost; and appeals. Merritt Parkway Files consist of signed vouchers, warranty deeds, title reports, abstract of title, mortgage documents, and blueprints of deed plans.
Series 3. Subject Files,,
Subgroup 4. Connecticut vs. Massachusetts, 1890-1932,
Subgroup 5. Francis A. Pallotti vs. William J. Cox, 1942,
Subgroup 6. Abele vs. Markle, 1947-1981,
Subgroup 7. Indian Litigation Files, 1666-2008,
Series 8. Opinions, 1899-1971, consists of opinions and related correspondence.
Series 9. Press Releases, 1983-1990,
Series 10. Corporation Penalty Letters, 1908-1940,
Series 11. Blueprints and Maps,,
Series 12. Highway Department Reports of Accidents, 1917-1922,
Series 13. Workmen's Compensation Case Files, circa 1936-1962, may include agreements; compensation agreements; correspondence; approvals or denials of claims; injury reports; report of accident or occupational disease to an employee; physicians and surgeons report of illness or injury to state employee; surgeon's report to commissioner in cases of permanent injury; report of changes in personnel; motor vehicle accident reports; Attorney General collection reports; legal documents; notices of hearings; medical certificates; cards; bills; receipts; lists; and notes.
Arrangement
Series 1. Correspondence, 1899-1947
Series 2. Case Files,
Series 3. Subject Files,
Subgroup 4. Connecticut vs. Massachusetts, 1890-1932
Subgroup 5. Francis A. Pallotti vs. William J. Cox, 1942
Subgroup 6. Abele vs. Markle, 1947-1981
Subgroup 7. Indian Litigation Files, 1666-2008
Series 8. Opinions, 1899-1971
Series 9. Press Releases, 1983-1990
Series 10. Corporation Penalty Letters, 1908-1940
Series 11. Blueprints and Maps,
Series 12. Highway Department Reports of Accidents, 1917-1922
Series 13. Workmen's Compensation Case Files, circa 1936-1962
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. Office of the Attorney General
Subjects:
Places:
Connecticut
Persons:
Averill, Ernest L.; Riddle, Clarine Nardi; Lieberman, Joseph I.
Document Types:
Briefs (legal documents); Clippings; Correspondence; Legal Documents; Maps; Notebooks; Photocopies; Publications; Reports
Restrictions on Access
Series 13. Workmen's Compensation Case Files, circa 1936-1962, are restricted due to Conn. Gen. Stat. sec. 1-210(b)(2) of the Freedom of Information Act which exempts from disclosure personnel or medical files and similar files the disclosure of which would constitute an invasion of personal privacy and Conn. Gen. Stat. sec. 1-210(b)(10) of the Freedom of Information Act which exempts from disclosure any records created as a result of a doctor-patient or a therapist-patient relationship.
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Correspondence, 1899-1947
  - 1984-087, 19 cubic feet
  - 1903
    - S-W, 1903-1906 (Box 19, Folder 1-6)
    - Y-Z, 1903-1906 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - 1907
    - A-K, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 1-11)
  - 1908
    - A-K, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 12-24)
  - 1909
    - A-H, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 25-32)
    - I-Z, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 1-12)
  - 1910
    - A-Z, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 13-34)
  - 1911
    - L-Z, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 35-43)
  - 1912
    - A-C, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 44-46)
    - D-Z, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 1-17)
  - 1917
    - List of foreign corporations failure to file annual reports, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - A-E, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 19-25)
    - G, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Highway claims, adjusted, 1917-1921 (Box 3, Folder 27-29)
    - H, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 30-31)
    - J, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - L-N, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 33-35)
    - P, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - R, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1918
    - A-H, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 2-9)
    - Highway Department, 1918-1922 (Box 4, Folder 10-12)
    - I-T, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 13-25)
    - W, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 26-27)
    - Z, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 1919
    - G, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Health Department, 1919-1921 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - H, 1919-1924 (Box 4, Folder 31-32)
    - A-C, 1919-1922 (Box 16, Folder 1-14)
    - Corporation taxes, 1919-1922 (Box 16, Folder 15-17)
    - D-F, 1919-1922 (Box 16, Folder 18-24)
    - H, 1919-1922 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
    - Highway Department - Bennett, 1919-1922 (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
    - K-M, 1919-1922 (Box 17, Folder 5-11)
    - Motor Vehicles, 1919-1922 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - N, 1919-1922 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Norwich State Hospital, 1919-1922 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - P, 1919-1922 (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
    - Public Utilities, 1919-1922 (Box 17, Folder 17-18)
    - R-T, 1919-1922 (Box 17, Folder 19-29)
    - V-W, 1919-1922 (Box 17, Folder 30-32)
  - 1920
    - A-B, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 33-34)
    - G, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - S-T, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 36-37)
    - V, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - 1921
    - A, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Athletic Commission, 1921-1928 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - B-C, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 41-42)
    - H, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - 1922
    - A-C, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 44-46)
    - F, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - H, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - M, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - P, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - S, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - W, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - 1923
    - A-C, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 53-55)
    - D, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - G-H, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
    - M-N, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
    - W, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - M-R, 1923-1926 (Box 19, Folder 8-12)
  - 1924
    - A-D, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 7-10)
    - F-H, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 11-13)
    - R, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - State Park Forest Commission, 1924-1927 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - W, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 1925
    - A-C, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 17-19)
    - F-H, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 20-22)
  - 1926
    - A-H, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 23-30)
    - L-M, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 31-32)
    - O-P, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 33-34)
    - R, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Treasury Department, 1926-1928 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - W, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - 1927
    - A-B, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 38-39)
    - Connecticut Agricultural College, 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Fitch's Home for Soldiers, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - State Police, 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - T, 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Tax Commissioner, 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - W, 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Water Commission, 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Attorney General, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Long Lane Farm, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Mansfield State Training School, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Medical Examining Board, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Motor Vehicles, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
    - Norwich State Hospital, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - N-P, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Matters of legislative action-cede land to federal government, 1927-1929 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - 1928
    - A, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Agencies and Institutions, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Agriculture, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Attorney General, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Auditors, State, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - B, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Banking Department, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - C, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Compensation Commission, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Comptroller, Office of, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Connecticut State Hospital, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - D, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Dairy and Food Department, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Dental Commissioners, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Domestic Animals Commissioner, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - E, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Education of Blind, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Education, Board of, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Election rulings, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 65-67)
    - Embalmers, Board of, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - F, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Farm, Connecticut State Farm for Women, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Finance and Control, Board of, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Fish and Game, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Florence Crittenton Mission, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Forest and Wildlife Commission, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - G, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Governor, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - H, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Hairdressers and Cosmeticians Commissions, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Healing Arts, State Board of, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Health, Department of, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - H.E. Kelley, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Highway Department, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 7-9)
    - I, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Insurance Commissioner, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - J-M, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 12-15)
    - Mansfield State Training School and Hospital, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Mc, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Medical Examining Board, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Motor Vehicles, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - N, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Natureopathic Examiners, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Norwich State Hospital, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - O, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Osteopathic Registration and Examination, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - P, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Park and Forest Commission, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Prohibition Department, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Public Welfare Department, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - R-S, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - State Prison, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - V, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Veteran's Home Commission, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - 1929
    - A-E, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 34-40)
    - G-N, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 1-11)
    - P, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - R-W, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 13-19)
    - Y-Z, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 1930
    - A, 1930-1931 (Box 7, Folder 21-26)
    - C-E, 1930-1931 (Box 8, Folder 1-6)
    - H-I, 1930-1931 (Box 8, Folder 7-14)
    - R-T, 1930-1931 (Box 8, Folder 15-19)
    - State Police Association, 1930-1933 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - D-F, 1930-1931 (Box 19, Folder 14-19)
  - 1931
    - A, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - I, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 21-25)
    - M, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - U-V, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 27-28)
    - W, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Y-Z, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 30-31)
    - Town Deposit Fund, 1931-1933 (Box 18, Folder 9-13)
  - 1932
    - A-B, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - I, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - M, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - R, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1933
    - A-H, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 6-31)
    - H-I, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 1-5)
    - K-M, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 6-10)
    - R-T, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 11-13)
    - Highway Department, 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 15-19)
    - M-O, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 20-24)
    - W, 1933-1935 (Box 18, Folder 25-26)
  - 1934
    - A-E, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 14-32)
    - E-M, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 1-26)
    - N-W, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 1-18)
  - 1935
    - A, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 19-27)
    - B-F, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 1-29)
    - H-M, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 1-29)
    - M-P, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 1-11)
    - R-W, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 12-34)
    - Y-Z, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 35-37)
  - 1984-094, 23 cubic feet
  - 1899-1902
    - No replies, 1899-1902 (Box 1)
      Does not include the letters L and U-Z.
  - 1903-1915
    - Correspondence, circa 1903-1915, undated (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1904-1909 (Box 35)
  - 1932
    - A [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 1)
    - Accountants, State Board of, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Adjutant General, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Aeronautics, Dept. of, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Agencies & Institutions, Dept. of, 1932 (Box 1)
    - American Legion, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Athletic Commission, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Auditors Folder, 1932 (Box 1)
    - B [Miscellaneous}, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Bank - The Commercial Trust Co. (Annette J. Berg), 1935 (Box 1)
    - Bank - The Commercial Trust Co. (Receivership) closed. [1], 1935-1936 (Box 1)
    - Bank - Commissioner, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Barbers, Board of Examiners of, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Bonds, 1932 (Box 1)
    - C [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 1)
    - Cedarcrest Sanitarium, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Child Welfare, Bureau of, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Chiropractic Board, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Comparative Sales Information (Report) (Real Estate Transactions), 1932 (Box 1)
    - Compensation Commissioners, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Comptroller, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut Agricultural College, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1931-1932 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut Federation of Labor, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut Reformatory, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut School For Boys, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut State Farm For Women, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut State Hospital, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Coroner’s Fees, 1932 (Box 1)
    - D [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2)
    - Dairy & Food Commission, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Dental Commission, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Domestic Animals, 1932 (Box 2)
    - E [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2)
    - Education, Board of, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Election, Rulings, Voting, etc., 1932 (Box 2)
    - F [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2)
    - Farm Bureau, Hartford Country, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Finance & Control, Board of, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Firearms Association, Connecticut State, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Fish & Game, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Fitch’s Home for Soldiers, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Forms For Deeds, etc., 1932 (Box 2)
    - G [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2)
    - General Assembly, 1931 (Box 2)
    - Governor, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Governor’s Foot Guard, 1932 (Box 2)
    - H [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2)
    - Hairdressers & Cosmeticians Commission, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Harbor Masters, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Healing Arts, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Health Dept., 1932 (Box 2)
    - Highway Dept., 1932; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - I [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2)
    - Insurance Commissioner, 1932 (Box 2)
    - J [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2)
    - Johnson, Raymond A., 1932 (Box 2)
    - Jones, H. Roger, 1930-1931 (Box 2)
    - Jones, H. Roger, 1932 (Box 2)
    - K [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2)
    - Kosicki, Bernard A., 1932 (Box 2)
    - L [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2)
    - Labor & Factory Inspection - Commissioner, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Library, State (Mr. Goddard), 1932 (Box 2)
    - Long Lane Farm, 1932 (Box 2)
    - M [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2)
    - Mansfield State Training School & Hospital, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Marriage Opinions, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Mc [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2)
    - Mc, 1929-1931 (Box 2)
    - Medical Hearing, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Midwives, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Motor Vehicles, Connecticut Board of Examiners of, 1931 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1932 (Box 2)
    - [Motor Vehicles - License Plates], 1931-1932 (Box 2)
    - Mystic Oral School for the Deaf, 1932 (Box 2)
    - N [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Natureopathic Board of Examiners, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Nurses, Board Of Examination & Registration, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - O [Miscellaneous], 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Odd Fellow’s Home - Groton, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Old Age Pension Folder, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Optometry, Board of Examiners of, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - P, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Pharmacy, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Police Department, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Prohibition Department, 1931-1932 (Box 2A)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Public Utility Delinquencies, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Public Welfare, Dept. of, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - R, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Revenue, Internal, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Rivers, Harbors & Bridges, Commissioners of, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - T, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Tax Commissioner, 1930-1932 (Box 2A)
    - Teachers Retirement Board, 1930-1932 (Box 2A)
    - Treasurer, 1930-1932 (Box 2A)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - U, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Unemployment Commission, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - V, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Veterans Administration, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Veterans Home Commission, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - W, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - Water Commission, 1932 (Box 2A)
    - X-Z, 1932 (Box 2A)
  - 1933
    - P [Miscellaneous], 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Park & Forest (State) Commission, 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Pharmacy, 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Proclamations, 1932-1933 (Box 2A)
    - Prohibition, 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Public Utility Delinquencies, 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Public Welfare, Dept. of, 1933 (Box 2A)
    - R [Miscellaneous], 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Raff Co. - Re: Shelton Tuberculosis Sanitorium., 1932-1933 (Box 2A)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corps., 1932 (Box 2A)
    - S [Miscellaneous], 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Secretary of State, 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Shell Fish Commission, 1933 (Box 2A)
    - State Police Association, 1933-1935 (Box 2A)
    - State Police Dept., 1933 (Box 2A)
    - State Prison., 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Superior Court (Lee vs. Callagari), 1933 (Box 2A)
    - T [Miscellaneous], 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Taxes - Inheritance & Estate Penalty Taxes, 1932-1933 (Box 2A)
    - Taxes - Penalty Tax Cases., 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Taxes - Special Tax Commission, 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Teachers Retirement Board, 1933 (Box 2A)
    - Treasurer, 1933 (Box 3)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, 1933 (Box 3)
    - Tuberculosis Sanitorium (Compensation Cases), 1933 (Box 3)
    - U [Miscellaneous], 1933 (Box 3)
    - United States Government (1931 - 1934) (Box 3)
    - V [Miscellaneous], 1933 (Box 3)
    - Veteran’s Home Commission, 1933 (Box 3)
    - Veterinarians, Board of Examiners, 1933 (Box 3)
    - W [Miscellaneous], 1933 (Box 3)
    - Water Commission., 1933 (Box 3)
    - X-Z, 1933 (Box 3)
  - 1936
    - A (Miscellaneous), 1936 (Box 3)
    - Acoustics - Hall of House, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Adjutant General, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Aeronautics, Commissioner of, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Agriculture, Dept. of (Conn.), 1936 (Box 3)
    - Attorney General, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Auditors, State, 1936 (Box 3)
    - B, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Banking Dept., 1936 (Box 3)
    - Bonds, In Re, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Budget, Correspondence in Re, 1936 (Box 3)
    - C (Miscellaneous), 1936 (Box 3)
    - Cedercrest Sanitarium, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Compensation Commissioner, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Comptroller, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut State College, Storrs, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut State Farm For Women, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut State Hospital, Middletown, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut State Prison, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut State Unemployment Act, Special Session of 1936 (Box 3)
    - Council of State Government, 1936 (Box 3)
    - D (Miscellaneous), 1936 (Box 3)
    - Dairy and Food Commissioner, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Dental Commissioner, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Deposit Slips, 1935-1936 (Box 3)
    - E (Miscellaneous), 1936 (Box 3)
    - Education, Board of, 1935-1936 (Box 3)
    - Election Rules, 1936 (Box 3)
    - Embalmers, 1936 (Box 4)
    - Emergency Relief Commission, 1936 (Box 4)
    - Engineers & Land Surveyors, State Board of Registration for, 1936 (Box 4)
    - F (Miscellaneous), 1935-1936 (Box 4)
    - Fairfield State Hospital, 1936 (Box 4)
    - Federal Home Loan Board, 1936 (Box 4)
    - Federal Housing Administration, 1936 (Box 4)
    - Finance And Control, Board of, 1935-1936 (Box 4)
    - Fish and Game Commission, 1936 (Box 4)
    - Fish and Game - Property of J. Lee, 1936 (Box 4)
    - Fitch’s home For Soldiers, 1936 (Box 4)
    - G (Miscellaneous), 1936 (Box 4)
    - Garnishments, 1936 (Box 4)
    - Governor, 1936 (Box 4)
    - Hairdresser’s & Cosmeticians, Commission, 1936 (Box 4)
    - Harbor Masters, 1936 (Box 4)
    - Highway Department, 1936 (Box 4)
    - Highway Insurance Claims, 1936 (Box 4)
  - 1937-1940
    - A (Miscellaneous), 1939 -1940 (Box 5)
    - Accountancy, State Board of, 1939 (Box 5)
    - Adjutant General, 1937-1940 (Box 5)
    - Aeronautics, Commissioner of, 1937-1941 (Box 5)
    - Agriculture, Dept. of (Conn.), 1934-1939 (Box 5)
    - Architectural Examining Board, 1937 (Box 5)
    - Armory, State, 1936-1940 (Box 5)
    - Athletic Commissioner, 1939-1940 (Box 5)
    - Attorney General, 1937-1940 (Box 5)
    - Auditors, State, 1938-1940 (Box 5)
    - B (Miscellaneous), 1936-1940 (Box 5)
    - Banking Dept., 1936-1940 (Box 5)
    - Barber, 1937-1940 (Box 5)
    - Blind - Board of Education of, 1936-1937 (Box 5)
    - Budget, Director of the, 1937-1939 (Box 5)
    - C (Miscellaneous), 1937-1939 (Box 5)
    - Chiropractic Board, 1937-1940 (Box 5)
    - Commission on Care & Treatment of People Afflicted with Physical or Mental Disabilities, 1939-1940 (Box 5)
    - Compensation Commissioner, 1937-1940 (Box 5)
    - Comptroller, 1937-1940 (Box 5)
    - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1937-1940 (Box 5)
    - Connecticut Medical Examining Board, 1937-1939 (Box 5)
    - Connecticut Reformatory, 1939-1940 (Box 5)
    - Connecticut Regional Market Authority, 1940 (Box 5)
    - Connecticut School For Boys, 1937 (Box 5)
    - Connecticut State Employment Service, 1937-1940 (Box 5)
    - Connecticut State Farm For Women, 1939-1940 (Box 5)
    - Connecticut State Hospital (Middletown), 1937-1940 (Box 5)
    - Connecticut State Prison, 1938-1940 (Box 5)
    - Connecticut Tree Protection Examining Board, 1946 (Box 5)
    - Coroners, 1937-1938 (Box 5)
    - Council of State Government, 1936-1940 (Box 5)
    - County Commissioners, 1936-1939 (Box 5)
    - D (Miscellaneous), 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - Dairy and Food Commissioner, 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - Dental Commission, 1936-1940 (Box 6)
    - Domestic Animals, Commission of, 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - E (Miscellaneous), 1937 (Box 6)
    - Education, Board of, 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - Election Matters, 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - Embalmers, 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - Engineers and Land Surveyors, State Board of Registration for, 1937-1939 (Box 6)
    - F (Miscellaneous), 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - Fairfield State Hospital, 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - Finance and Control, Board of, 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - Fish and Game Commission, 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - Fitch’s Home for Soldiers, 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - G (Miscellaneous), 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - General Assembly, 1939 (Box 6)
    - Governor, 1937-1940 (Box 6)
    - H (Miscellaneous), 1937-1939 (Box 6)
    - Hairdressers and Cosmeticians, 1937-1939 (Box 6)
    - Harbor Commissioners, 1939-1940 (Box 6)
    - Health Dept., 1936-1940 (Box 6)
    - Highway Dept., 1935-1937 (Box 6)
    - Highway Dept., 1938 (Box 7)
    - Highway Dept., 1939 (Box 7)
    - Highway Dept., 1940 (Box 7)
    - Homeopathic Medical Examining Board, 1938 (Box 7)
    - Insurance Dept., 1937-1940 (Box 7)
    - Israel Putnam Memorial Camp Ground Commission, 1939 (Box 7)
    - J (Miscellaneous), 1937-1939 (Box 7)
    - Judicial Dept., 1938-1939 (Box 7)
    - Juvenile Courts, 1939 (Box 7)